-告诉他  -就告诉他嘛
- Tell him. - Just tell him.
-闭嘴  -告诉我什么
- Shut up. - Tell me what?
你看你  连正眼看他都不敢
Look at you, you won't even look at him.
就告诉我吧
Oh, come on tell me.
下回有女人不肯看我  我也好有新理由
I could use another reason why women won't look at me.
好吧  好吧  昨晚我梦见
All right. All right. Last night, I had a dream that uh...
我和你
...that you and I were
在这桌上做爱
doing it on this table.
梦里干的不错嘛
Excellent dream score.
你怎会有这种梦
Why would you dream that?
最重要的是
More importantly...
我棒吗
...was I any good?
简直是棒极了
Well, you were pretty damn good.
真有意思  在我梦中我非常力不从心
Interesting. Cause in my dreams, I'm surprisingly inadequate.
昨晚你在这桌上的表现完美无缺
Last night, you seemed to know your way around the table.
真高兴能与你们分享
I love it when we share.
你没事吧
You okay there?
我不敢相信你会在她梦中做爱
I can't believe you two had sex in her dream.
抱歉  仅此一次
I'm sorry, it was a one-time thing.
我醉得不省人事  而且这不是我的潜意识
I was very drunk, and it was someone else's subconscious.
你好呀  瑞秋
Hello, Rachel.
下去
Get off.
给我  你们能想像我操作钻床的样子吗
Ooh, give me. Can you see me operating a drill press?
不知道  你当时穿什么
I don't know. What are you wearing?
菲比  你为何想操作钻床
Phoebe, why would you want to operate a drill press?
只是暂时的工作
Just for some short-term-work.
直到我找回一部分前按摩客户
You know, until I get back some of my massage clients.
又是海盗吗
Pirates again?
不  根本不贴边
No. Nothing like that.
我真是个大笨蛋
I'm just such a dummy.
我教他们"自己在家动手做按摩"
I taught a "Massage Yourself at Home" workshop.
结果他们就不来了
And they are.
嗨  钱德勒  她可以为你工作
Hey, Chan, she could work for you.
谢了  乔伊  这是个好主意
Thanks, Joey. That's a good idea.
我可以  我来吧  什么工作
I could. I could do it. What is it?
我秘书这几周无法来上班
My secretary's gonna be out for a couple of weeks.
她去给一侧乳房动消乳手术
She's having one of her boobs reduced.
一言难尽的波霸故事
It's a whole big boob story.
我可以当个秘书
I could be a secretary.
菲比  我不知你是否是这块料
Phoebes, I don't know if it's your kinda thing...
因为这份工作需要你大部分时间
... because it involves a lot being normal
尽可能保持正常
for a large portion of the day.
我能办到
I could do that.
-你玩什么呢  -我的新传呼机
-What are you playing with? -It's my new beeper.
古生物学家要那玩意儿干嘛
What the hell does a paleontologist need a beeper for?
以防恐龙紧急事件  救命啊  快来
Is it like for dinosaur emergencies? Help. come quick,
他们还是绝种了
They're still extinct.
不  是为卡罗尔生产买的
No. It's for when Carol goes into labor.
好让她随时联系到我
She can get me wherever I am.
她只需拨号55-金宝
All she has to do is dial 55-Jimbo.
这号码真酷  还能当孩子的名字
A cool number and a possible name for the kid.
-各位回头见了  -去见小伊森吗
- All right, I'll see you guys later. - Off to see young Ethan?
谢谢
Thank you.
伊森到底有多小  很小吗
How young is young Ethan? Young?
年纪和我们差不多
He's our age.
当我们还是
When we were...
-他是大学四年级学生  -大学
- He's a senior in college. - College?
这位小朋友不在乎你的年纪吗
This man-child has no problem with how old you are?
当然不在乎  这根本不是问题
No, of course not. It's not even an issue...
因为我告诉他我22岁
...because I told him I was 22.
-你什么  -什么
- You what? - What?
-我不像22岁吗  -25  26还说得过去
- Oh, I can't pass for 22? - Well, maybe 25, 26.
-我本来就26  -那就对啦
- I am 26. - There you go.
-听见没  -听见了
- Can you hear that? - Yeah.
知道不  拿起电话就不会响了
You see, that'll stop when you pick up the phone.
-我来了  -好的
- Oh, I'm on. - Okay.
宾先生办公室
Mr. Bing's office.
抱歉  他正在开会.
No, I'm Sorry, he's in a meeting right now.
我没在开会  我在...
I'm not in a meeting. I'm right... Whoops.
他知道这件事吗
Will he know what this is in reference to?
他有你的号码吗
And he has your number?
好  我会转告他的  再见
I'll see that he gets the message. Bye-bye.
罗斯打来问候的
Ross says hi.
真好玩  好了  我们现在做什么
This is so fun. All right. What do we do now?
现在我得开始工作了
Well, now I actually have to get to work.
"可能吧"
"Most likely."
好了  我出去了
Okay, I'm gonna be out there.
好的  再见
All right. Bye-bye.
再见
Bye-bye.
-什么事  -你在干嘛
- Yes? - What you doing?
窗户擦好了  蜡烛点上了
Okay, windows are clean. Candles are lit.
皮带太紧  我得去换一条
Belt's too tight. Gotta change the belt.
鱼翻过没  没  因为我做的意大利面
Did I turn the fish? Nope, because I made lasagna.
-我有没有失控  -有一点点
- Am I out of control? - Just a touch.
莫妮卡  我不明白
Mon, I don't understand.
你跟这个男生从他期中考试后
I mean, you've been dating this guy since like, what...
谈到现在
... his midterms.
为什么  突然
Why, all of a sudden, are you so...?
-我怎么了  -今晚会是销魂一夜吗
- What? - Could tonight be the night?
我不知道  他是个好男孩
I don't know. He's a great guy...
我喜欢和他在一起  但是很难说
...and I love being with him. But, you know...
只能顺其自然  无法预先计划好
...things happen when they happen. You don't plan these things.
-腿毛刮了没  -刮了
- So, did you shave your legs? - Yeah.
罗斯  别纠结了  这只是一场梦
Would you let it go, Ross? It was just a dream.
不代表...
It doesn't mean
时候到了  宝宝要出世了
This is it. Oh my God! It's baby time! Baby time!
放轻松  冷静点  别紧张
All right, relax. Just relax. Be cool.
对  刚有人呼我
Yeah, hi. I was just beeped.
不  安卓不在这  今天呼错三次了
No, Andre is not here. Third time today.
对  我确定
Yes, I am sure.
不 先生  我不提供那些服务
No, sir, I do not perform those kind of services.
服务
Services?
懂了  服务嘛
Oh, services.
对  你要呼的是55-劲爆
Yeah, you want 55-Jumbo.
没错
That's right.
没错  是劲爆不是金宝  先生
That's right. JUMBO with a "U," sir.
不  相信我  你不会想要我的
No, belive me, You don't want me.
从他的号码看来  你看到我会大失所望
Judging by his number, I'd be a huge disappointment.
好吧  再见了
Alrighty, bye-bye.
第一天上班如何
How was the first day?
太棒了  每个人都非常非常好
Excellent. Everyone was so, so nice.
瞧  认识我这种职位的人多沾光
It pays to know the man who wears my shoes.
说的是我
Me.
不  我没告诉任何人我认识你
No. I didn't tell anyone I knew you.
-为什么   -因为  你懂的
- Why not? - Well, because, you know.
他们并不喜欢你
They don't like you.
-什么  -我以为你早知道
- What? - I thought you knew that.
-谁不喜欢我  -每个人
- No, who doesn't like me? - Everyone.
除了
Except for....
不  每个人
No. Everyone.
-你在说什么啊  -别难过
- What are you talking about? - Don't feel bad.
他们过去都很喜欢你
They used to like you a lot.
自从你升职后
But then you got promoted, and, you know,
他们感觉你是上司  大人物
now you're like Mr. Boss Man. you know, Mr. Big.
宾先生  宾大老板
Mr. Bing. Boss Man Bing.
-真不敢相信  -他们甚至还模仿你
- I can't believe it. - Yeah. They even do you.
模仿我
They "do" me?
对  比如这样
You know, like, okay:
报告要"何时"才能交来
"Could that report be any later?"
-我没有那样说话  -你有的
- I don't sound like that. - Yeah, you do.
这山谷回荡着美妙的
"The hills are alive with the sound...
"音乐"声
...of music."
我的烤饼  "我"的烤饼
"My scone. My scone."
我没那样说话  这绝"不"是真的
I don't sound like that. That is so not true.
"不"是这样  "不"是这样
That is so not... That is so not...
这 闭嘴吧
That Oh, shut up.
-不会吧  -告诉你  我到九岁时
- Did not. - I'm telling you, up until I was 9...
还以为"枪口"就是真实存在的犯罪现场
... I thought "gunpoint" was an actual place where crimes happened.
-怎么会  -新闻老是报导犯罪事件
- How's that possible? - Well, think about it. It's always on the news.
某人在"枪口"下
"A man is being held up at Gunpoint."
惊慌的观光客在"枪口"下
"Tourists are terrorized at Gunpoint."
我一直在想  怎么还有人去那儿
And I kept thinking, "Why do people continue to go there?"
-我该走了  -好
- I should go. - Ok.
-除非  -什么
- Unless. - What?
除非你要在这儿过夜
Unless you wanna stay over.
我反正要在这过夜  不如
I mean, I'm going to. So....
是啊  这样再好不过
Yeah, I'd really like that.
在我们考虑留宿的事宜之前
Before we get into any staying-over stuff...
我有些事情必须告诉你
...there's something you should know.
是"我明天一早有课"之类的
Ok. Is this, like, "I have an early class tomorrow"...
还是"我与山羊秘密结婚了"
...or "I'm secretly married to a goat"?
在这两者之间
Well, it's somewhere in between.
就严格技术层面而言  当然  我还没
You see, in a strictly technical sense, of course, I'm not....
我是说  我还没有
Well, I mean, I haven't ever....
-伊森  -在
- Ethan? - Yeah.
你是处男吗
Are you a virgin?
如果你们这些孩子现在这样称呼的话
If that's what you kids are calling it these days, then...
对  我是个处男
...yes, I am.
我大概一直在等待适合的人
I've kind of been waiting for the right person.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
你知道我是在指你吧
You do know I was talking about you, right?
你一直喔个不停
You keep saying that.
你懂的  你在杂志上看过  在电影里看过
You know, you read about it. You see it in the movies.
甚至在家里练习过  可是天啊
Even when you practice it at home, man, oh, man...
这感觉实在没得比
...it is nothing like that.
听着  听着
Listen, listen.
你对我坦白了一件难以启齿的事
You told me something that was really difficult for you.
我想如果你能坦诚相对  那我也能
And I figure if you can be honest, then I can too.
天啊  别告诉我刚才做错了
Oh, God. Don't tell me I did it wrong.
不  那件事你做得非常完美
No, no, no. Nothing wrong about that.
好  我说了
Ok, Here goes.
我不是22岁
I'm not 22.
我是25岁
I'm 25...
零13个月
...and 13 months.
但是我想  我们的关系不会因此变掉
But I figure, you know, that shouldn't change anything.
年龄根本就不是距离对吧
I mean, what the hell does it matter how old we are?
听着
Listen...
在你坦承之际
...as long as we're telling stuff...
我也有话要说
... I have another one for you.
我比你所知的年纪还小
I'm a little younger than I said.
-你不是四年级生吗  -我是四年级
- You're not a senior? - Oh, I'm a senior...
高中四年级
...in high school.
我们不应该这样
What we did was wrong.
天啊  我刚和一个
God, I just had sex with
不到二十岁的小屁孩做爱了
someone who wasn't alive during the bicentennial.
我刚做爱了
I just had sex.
伊森  注意听  你为何不早告诉我
Ethan, focus. How could you not tell me?
-你也没告诉我你真实年龄  -那不一样
- You never tell me how old you are. - It's different.
我撒的谎不会让我们在48个州获重罪
My lie didn't make one of us a felon in 48 states.
-你到底在想什么  -我什么都没想
- What were you thinking? - I wasn't thinking.
-我只是忙于  -不要说
- I was too busy falling... - Don't say it.
爱上你
...in love with you.
-真的吗  -对不起
- Really? - Sorry.
好吧  别再爱我了
Well, fall out of it.
你都不该在这  你该在学校过夜的
You shouldn't be here. It's a school night.
天啊
Oh, God.
我就像是那种
I'm like those women that you see...
专门勾引小帅哥的女人
...with shiny guys named Chad.
我成了琼·柯琳斯
I'm Joan Collins.
谁
Who?
好  安卓45分钟后就会到
Ok. Andre should be there in about 45 minutes.
就这样  再见
Alrighty. Bye-bye.
这样省事多了
It's just easier that way.
说吧  你昨晚的梦都告诉我了
Come on. You told me about the last dream.
不  忘了吧
No. Forget it.
为什么  难道是梦中的我对你过于粗鲁
Why not? Was I doing something particularly saucy?
好吧  我说
All right. Fine.
梦中不仅仅你在场
You were not the only one there.
乔伊也在场
Joey was there too.
好的
All right.
那
Was there...
还有其他人吗
...anybody else there?
-没有  -你确定没有人...
- No. - You sure? Nobody...
发发薄荷糖啥的
... handing out mints or anything?
没有  只有我们三个
No, it was just the three of us.
说说看  是你跟钱德勒做完
So, tell me. Was it like you and Chandler,
然后跟我做  还是我们三个同时
...and then you and me, or you, me and Chandler?
-你知道吗  -什么
- You know what? - What?
有几次
There were times...
我都没有参与
...when it wasn't even me.
真甜蜜  伙计们
That is so sweet, you guys.
莫妮卡  伊森又来电话了
Mon, Ethan called again.
-莫妮卡  -莫妮卡
- Mon? - Mon！
-干嘛  -伊森又来电话了
- What? - Ethan called again.
-你不再见他了吗  -对
- You're not seeing him anymore? - No.
有时候  有些问题无法解决
Sometimes, things don't work out.
这跟他需要假条才能翘掉体育课无关吗
This has nothing to do with him needing a note to get out of gym?
我没说  什么都没说  我发誓
I, I didn't say any... I sw... I did not say anything. I swear.
-他听到的  -听着  下回见到他时
- He stopped by. - Listen, next time you talk to him...
能问问《恐龙战队》中最强的是谁吗
...could you ask him which one the strongest Power Ranger is?
我的生活真是太精彩了  换个话题行吗
Oh, my life is just so amusing. Can we drop it now?
对不起
Sorry.
墨菲时间到了
"It's morphin'time."
-暴龙  -剑龙
- Stegosaurus. - Tyrannosaurus.
我得走了
I gotta go.
天  脑充血
Head rush.
再一次  我真得走了
One more, and then I have to go.
酷
Cool.
你要上哪儿去
Where you going?
我要和几个同事去参加生日会
I got a birthday party with some work people.
同事吗  没人跟我说
Work people? Nobody told me.
我知道  这都是因为
No, I know. That's part of the whole...
他们不喜欢你所造成的
...you know, them-not-liking-you extravaganza.
你来说说  我真不明白
You know what, I don't get this.
一个月前  他们都是我朋友
A month ago, these people were my friends.
我当上了主管并不代表我会变成另一个人
You know, just I'm in charge doesn't mean I'm a different person.
那你今晚该来
Well, then you should come tonight.
和他们多相处
You know, just hang out with them.
让他们知道你还是个大好人
Let them see what a great guy you still are.
-你认为我该去  -真心的  你该去
- You think I should? - I really do. Yeah.
-那好  -走吧
- Ok. - Ok.
我们能不一起去吗
But could we not go together?
我不想成为邀请上司的怪人
I don't wanna be the geek who invited the boss.
昨晚真是太棒了
I think last night was great.
我和崔西合唱了首《乌木与象牙》
You know, the Karaoke thing. Tracy and I doing Ebony and Ivory.
你表现得很好
You were great.
但大家仍然取笑你
But they still made fun of you.
-什么  -你现在成了"假惺惺"老板
- What? - You know, now you're more like, Mr. Caring Boss.
"套近乎"老板
Mr. I'm-one-of-you Boss.
"称兄道弟"宾大老板
Mr. I-wanna-be-your-buddy Boss Man Bing.
我真是想不通
Then I don't get it.
你知道吗钱德勒  你得面对现实
You know what Chandler? I think you just gotta face it.
你坐在这间大办公室里
You're like the guy in the big office.
有权录取他们  也有权开除他们
You're the one that hires and fires them.
-他们说你还是个好上司  -是吗
- They still say you're a great boss. - They do?
但是他们不再是你的朋友
Uh uh. But they're not your friends anymore.
-我只是想  -但你不能
- I just want - But you can't.
但我只是想
But I just want
你不是要去...
Aren't you gonna?
卡罗尔和我定了新暗号
Carol and I have a new system.
如果她打911
If she punches in 9-1-1...
就代表她将生产  否则我就根本不理会
it means she's having a baby. Otherwise, I just ignore it.
那安卓呢
What about Andre?
早上他接到个电话
Oh, well this morning he got a call from
我觉得是表弟纳森打来的
who I think was our cousin Nathan,
老实说  我知道太多内幕了
and frankly, it was a little more than I needed to know.
-嗨  -我本打算这么说的
-Hi. - That was gonna be my opener.
你们看过洗手间里的新烘手机没
Hey, did you guys check out those new hand dryers in the bathroom?
-我以为那只是谣传  -千真万确
- I thought that was just a rumor. - True story.
行了  我得和你谈谈
All right. Look, I gotta tell you something.
我不是17岁
I'm not 17.
我这样说是为了让你觉得我可爱惹人怜
I only said that so you'd think I was cute and vulnerable.
其实我今年30
I'm actually 30.
娶了老婆  有正经工作  是个国会议员
I have a wife and a job. I'm your congressman.
莫妮卡  这太荒谬了  我们多般配
Monica, this is ridiculous. We're great together.
我们聊天  说笑  做爱也很协调
We can talk, we make each other laugh, and the sex....
我虽然经验不多  但一切是那么完美
I have no frame of reference, but I thought that was great.
-的确是  -那问题在哪儿
- It was. - Then what's the problem?
伊森  这太
Ethan, it's....
倒人胃口
It's icky.
"倒人胃口"
"Icky"?
就因为"倒人胃口"你就想放弃吗
You're actually gonna throw this away because it's "icky"?
我也很难过  我多希望情况不是这样
This isn't easy for me either. I wish things were different.
如果你年长几岁  或者我年轻几岁
If you were a few years older or I was a few years younger...
或是我们生活在圣经时代
...or we lived in biblical times...
-我就可以...  -不  不要说
- ...I could really - No, don't say it.
爱你
Love you.
-你的手还没干是吧  -还是湿的
- Are your hands still wet? - Moist.
那我们再去烘一次
Let's dry them again.
或者是  这些鸡尾酒"能"再烈一点吗
Or like, "Could these margaritas be any stronger?"
你好  钱德勒
Hey, Chandler.
你好  宾先生
Hello, Mr. Bing.
你昨晚唱的史提夫·汪达那首歌真好听
Loved your Stevie Wonder last night.
谢谢  听着  有关周数据的事
Thanks. Listen, about the weekly numbers,
九点"之"前请送到我办公室来
I'm gonna need them on my desk by 9:00.
-好的  -没问题
- Sure. - No problem.
总得给他们些话题嘛
You have to give them something.
刚刚是格斯顿  山托斯
That was Gerston, Santos,
留胡子的那个叫什么
and who's the guy with the moustache?
-派崔  -派崔  对
- Petrie. - Petrie. Right, okay.
看来这周末得有人
Well, some people are gonna be working...
"加"班了
...this weekend.
真好
Oh, that's nice.
罗斯
Ross.
我在这里
I'm here.
你在吗
You are?
我们刚在
We were just....
什么
What?
-这下可好  我有宝宝了  -什么
- Great. Now I'm having a baby. - What?
我要有宝宝了  我要有一个
I'm having a baby. I'm having a
-电话  电话在哪  -不在我这
- The phone, the phone. - I don't have the phone.
-罗斯  -我受伤了
-Ross? - I'm hurt.
莫妮卡  快走  各位快点  她要生了
Mon, Let's go. Come on, people. Woman in labor.
罗斯  看我这样子
Ross, Look what I've got going here.
坐车时再闹吧  行不
Save it for the cab. Ok?
你在干什么  我们要去医院
What are you doing? We're going to a hospital.
我不能打扮漂亮吗  说不定有帅医生
What, so I can't look nice? There might be doctors there.
-乔伊  别翻冰箱了  -好吧
- Joey, get out of the fridge. - All right.
-那是干嘛的  -路上吃的
- What is that? - For the ride.
-比如坐车的时候  -忍着
- Like in a cab - Save it.
-真讨厌  -莫妮卡  快  该走了
- Hating this. - Monica, come on. Let's go.
宝宝就要出世了
Baby coming.
我真不敢相信我要当姑姑了
I can't believe I'm gonna be an aunt.
-我要有侄子了  -真感人  走吧
- I'll have like a nephew. - That's nice. Get out.
行啦  我在走  我在走
All right, I'm going. I'm going.
走吧  赶紧
Here we go. Come on.